mountunestore.com 2010-06-13

# Privacy

Revolve Technologies Ltd are committed to protecting the privacy of anyone using our site and the confidentiality of any information that you provide us with. The purpose of this statement is to set out how we use any personal information that we may obtain from you. 

Data Protection Act 1988 

We are registered under the Data Protection Act and comply with the Act in all our dealings with your personal data. 

Use and collection of personal information 

In general you can visit our website without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. If, however, you use our site you will need to register and you will be asked to provide certain information such as your contact details. We will store this data and hold it on computer or otherwise. 

We may use information that you provide: 

(a)   To register you with our website and to administer it. 

(b)   For assessment and analysis e.g. marketing, customer and product analysis, to enable us to review, develop and improve our services. 

Cookies 

There is a technology called “cookies” which may be used by us to provide you with, for example, customised information from our website. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser which may then store it on your system. If you wish, you can usually adjust your browser so that your computer does not accept cookies. Please remember cookies do not contain confidential information such as your home address, telephone number or credit card details. We do not exchange cookies with any third party websites or external data suppliers. 

Security 

We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of any data that you disclose online and we will not be responsible for any breach of security unless this is due to our negligence or wilful default. 

General 

You have the right to see personal data (as defined under the Data Protection Act) that we keep about you upon receipt of a written request and payment of a fee of £10. Any request should be sent to: 

The Company Secretary 

Revolve Technologies Limited 

Prospect Way 

Hutton 

Brentwood 

Essex CM13 1XA
